Now you will create an
AI assistant from scratch that will perform
tasks for your business and personal life.
I personally fired my assistant because
this thing does her job
much better, cheaper, and more efficiently.  And
now you will create it using my ready-made
file, template and instructions.  Anyway,
let me show you how it works.
Let's imagine a real situation.
Listen, I'm at a party right now and I
met some guy.  He
says that a representative of the Black
Rock fund is offering us investments.  You
can find out what kind of fund this is and
whether it makes sense for us to meet with it.
Let's imagine a real situation.  I
met someone, I need to find out something, who
it is, should I talk to him.
He goes online, quickly finds some
information and within seconds
comes back with an answer, telling me that
this is a serious company, it has 11
trillion in money and that this could be a
unique opportunity to collaborate with
such guys.  Well, that's cool.  Okay,
then let's do it this way.
Wow, then
a meeting with a representative of this fund is scheduled for February 17th at 3:00 pm.  We've
given a task, we see how our assistant
is thinking, and now we'll go to the calendar,
where there's no event, but now it
will appear, I don't touch anything with my hands, and
it's already here.  We see that a message has arrived
in Telegram, and here we see a
meeting signed as required at the
time I requested.  Well,
let's try giving him one more
task.  For example,
write to my partner Vova and tell him that
we have a meeting with potential investors on February 17th and
that we need a
project prototype by then.  And be sure to
let him take his laptop with him.  I'll pick
him up in an hour.  See you.
We asked him to write to our
partner, without telling him where to write, and
roughly sketched out the text.  And now what do we
see?  He went to the database.  He went to
look through his contacts to find Vova,
my partner, there.  Now it will send
the process to the agent's email so that the
letter will arrive.  Here we see that the letter
was sent,
which the assistant informed us about.
Let's go to Vova's post office and see
what we have there.  And then a letter arrived with the subject:
meeting with investors on February 17.  Vova,
well, we have a meeting with investors from the
Black Rock fund.  A prototype is needed by this
time.  Take the laptop, Tom.  That is,
the assistant signed everything for us and completed
the task flawlessly.  And now you can do
it in less than half an hour from scratch.  You
don't need to know the code for this
construction set, where you just
move the blocks like LEGO.  You'll be putting together something like this that's
much more difficult
because this assistant can evolve
to the state of Jarvis, like Iron
Man.  And I will give you all the templates for this
, they are in my Telegram.  So, if you have
n't watched the previous lesson, I recommend you
watch it.  There will also be a link below,
because that's where we created this
little, simple assistant
that can accept
simple text requests and search for
information on the internet via Telegram.  And this is important in order to
understand the constructor on
which we do all this.  And the constructor
is called N8N.
This is an open source project
.  It allows us to internally connect
multiple different neural networks using IP
keys and customize the system
so that our assistant, for example,
can
monitor our calendar, communicate with
people, perform various work tasks,
write posts, and create scripts for our
videos on social networks.  And he can do everything that a
person can do, he can
self-learn.  And this is without
programming - this is the world in
which we already find ourselves.  Let's
start from scratch.  What are we
going to do?  You and I find ourselves on the
N8N website.  You just go to Google and
search for it, and when you sign up,
you have 14 days free.  We
find ourselves in our project.  What do we
see here in the main window?  We see the
Workflows section.  These are the working windows where
we will directly
launch our neural networks.  Next, Credentials
is a connection to various
external neural networks or sites, such as
Google mail, Google sheets, Google
calendar, yes, in order to manage all of this
.  Executions is the history of
launches.  That is, we
can look at each process like this now, yes,
green blocks were moving in front of you.
I did this on purpose so that it would be clear
how each process is processed.  And
look at the execution time of the processes.
That is, 3 seconds, 7 seconds, 19 seconds.   It will take
a person a while to remember Vova there, a while to
write a message, a while to find
information.  Well, a human is no longer
cool for work.  That's why we're going to
do something cool with you.  Click
Create workflow.  And the first thing we
do is click on the three dots and click
Import from file.  Let's take our finished
file.  I have a
templates folder on my desktop, and materials from which
I upload to my Telegram channel.  There
is business here.  assistant.  Here.  And in the
business assistant we have several
files.  It's all a system of agents.  That is,
now it is not even one assistant, but
several assistants connected to each
other.  So we select main,
select our main file, and a
ready-made template for our
assistant opens.  Here we immediately sign
it so that we don’t get confused or
lost later.  This is an important point for
organizing the work process.  That's it, we
renamed it.  We have
saved the automatic project.  Wonderful.  We
already have it here.  Let's take a closer
look at what it is and what it
looks like.  We have Telegramtgr first.  That
is, we have connected a Telegram bot through which
we communicate with our assistant.
Okay, we saw that.  Next we see
that the audio file is downloaded and
converted into text.  If we sent
an audio message, which is what we actually
did when communicating with our
assistant, because it is
much more convenient to communicate by voice.  neural networks, and those like,
uh, GPT, which we connected here
as brains, they cannot understand
voice, they only understand symbols,
only text.  Therefore, if we
send a voice message,
NeroNet first decrypts it.  And
we can see this process here.
If we double-click, we'll see that
Open AI has a model
that converts audio into
text and sends it to our
business assistant.  If we write it directly in text
, the request goes straight through and
ends up with our assistant.
So, let's figure out with him what's
going on here.  Our
assistant has brains.
Brains are GPT4O.  This is a model that
thinks, that makes all the decisions.
We rent it from Open AI.  It
costs us some money, but in
reality it costs mere pennies.  And considering
how much we earn from this, it’s even
, well, indecent.  So there it’s like
, well, you throw in 10 dollars, and
then it’s enough for a shitload of requests.
Therefore, it is the brain, it is memory.  In the previous
lecture, the link to which is below, I
talked about how such assistants are
structured, and how all of this is
connected from scratch.  So now we'll
focus on the most important things:
how it works with Google
Calendar, how it connects to an
external service, how
it works with email, how it works with the
contact database, and how it knows
who to write to.  Here.  And let's connect this.
This means that when our request comes into
Telegram, it is sent to our
business assistant, who has a
system prompt.  This is an instruction.  These are the
rules by which our assistant
operates.  And here we can read
what is written: "You are a personal
assistant. Your job is to choose the
right tools."  Now you have an
email agent to write
emails.  You have a calendar
agent to manage your
calendar.  You have a tool for
searching the internet.  Getting a little
ahead of myself, I'll say that
I also connect assistants to this assistant who write
posts for my Telegram channels, who
analyze competitors, and who
conduct research on the internet.  That
is, what we are going to create now
is a universal blank.  This is someone
we can communicate with.  And then we can
give him thousands of different tools and
hundreds of different
other assistants with which he can
communicate in order to complete the task.  So,
if he received a request that we need to
create a meeting in the calendar, he knows
that he doesn’t need to create
the meeting himself, he needs to contact the
calendar agent.  Let's double-click on it and
see that it is an agent calendar
that is connected to another page.
That is, when something needs to be done with the calendar
, it sends a request there.  This is
where we can get this agent.  To do this, we
return to the projects with you, we go
back.  Here we click save so as
not to lose anything.  And again we click
create workflows.  And we are creating a
new assistant with you.  Click on the three dots.
Import from file.  Let's take, in fact, the
same files that are available for free in my
Telegram channel.  And here we select the
main calendar.
So, we have deployed an assistant for
working with the calendar.  Let's
sign it right away too,
so we don't get confused later.  This is important
because there
will be automatic names, then you will get lost, and you
need everything to be convenient.  What do we
see here?  We see that he starts
working when he receives an external
request, when another workflow, when
another assistant calls him for help.
His task is working.
There is a system prompt inside here, that is, an
instruction according to which it operates.
It says that you are an assistant for working with
the calendar, you have such and such tasks.
You open my file, and you have everything
filled in right away.  He has
brains.  Also a model from Openi.  How does it
connect?  Very easy.  When
this template unfolds for you, you
press everything twice.  If you
already have an account connected here, then you simply
select the desired account and everything works.
If it’s not connected, then click Create
New Creedential and follow the instructions,
basically mine, to connect a new
account.  All.  Yes.
But here below is the most interesting thing,
because below
we see that he can create new
events, that he can create
events with other people, that he
can update them, delete them, well, in short, he
can work with our Google
calendar.  And how does he manage to do this, interestingly enough
?  Yes, it's very simple.  Google and
many other services allow us to
do all this calmly.  Here.  And for
this to work, what do we need?   To make things
easier and more convenient for you, I created a new Google
account, a completely new one.  And now you and I
will go straight through.  What are we
doing?  We go to Google and type in
Google Cloud Console in the search.  Here.  And here we
see platforms.
Accordingly, we immediately follow
this link.  So what do we have here?  Here
I'm already logged into my new
Google account, but I do
n't have anything set up yet.  Where did we
end up anyway?  We've landed on a page
that allows us to integrate with
various services.  And first we need to
click select a project.  We need to
make a new project here because
we don't have anything yet.  We see that we have
nothing here yet.  We click New
Project.  Here we closely follow what
I do.  Here.  And here we have an
automatic name created.
Excellent, let it be.  We don't choose the location
.
And now we are waiting for a new project to be created
.  We will make a connection inside this project
.
That's it, the project has been created.  Click on select
project to go to it.
So, we moved on to our project.  We see
that we have created something here.   It's
all complicated, confusing, lots of icons,
lots of new stuff, but you shouldn't get lost
or worry about it, because
we're not really interested in all of that.
What exactly are we interested in?  on the left
in this list.  If you have it
closed, then there are three stripes here.
You click on them, and it opens up
, uh, here's the menu list.  We see
IP and services here.  And here it
says AP in big letters.  And here we
hover with the mouse and see
library.  This is a library.  Here we press
here, boo.  And we moved to the list of IP
connections.  Here we need to go down
a little lower to find
Google services.  Here is Google Workspace.  And
we see here right away Google
Calendar.  This is what we need.  We
need to connect to Google Calendar.  And
we see here a bold, highlighted
enable button.  From my lessons we already know that
if something is unclear, you need to look for a
bold, brightly highlighted button.  She will
lead us to the result no matter what.   We're waiting
.
[music]
Still being created.  I want to say that the
time we find ourselves in is a
wonderful time, because without any
programming, from scratch, any
person can create
absolutely anything.  Jarvis himself, the
real thing, to replace employees in his
business.  Beauty.  So, create
credentials.  Bright button.  Click on
it.  What do we see here?  We are
required to fill in some data.  We're
not touching anything here for now.  Here
we see that there is user data and
application data.  But if we hover over the
question mark, we'll see that, well, that
means you and I can't
choose one of these sections.
In short, what do we need here?  USA.
Correct, probably, register, right?
Click Next.
Now we need to come up with a name for
our application.  The name of
our application will be called
assistant.
Here we select our mail and
start scrolling down.  Logo is not
required.  Developer contact
information is required.  Here
we enter, in general, our own email.
Now we click save and continue,
and our connection is created.  All.  You and I have
established a connection.  This
means that everything
will be working for us soon.  We click done,
application type web application.
We have the name substituted.  It may seem like
everything is complicated here, but you just walk
straight through.  Here, in fact, everything is
marked.  Whatever you absolutely must
fill out will be
highlighted here in any case.  Click
create.  Bold bright button.  Op.  And we have a
code.  Do you know what this code is?
This is precisely the key that we
need to use in order to
connect to N8N, to our
constructor.  That's it, you and I
pressed everything, and it seems like everything is
connected.  Here are the
credentials.  If we click here, we will
see that we have a
web client connection.  This is exactly what we have just
created together.  If we click on it
, we'll see that it has a
name, yes, Webclient 1. Now, if we
click on Audi here on the left, we
can see test users here.
And if we don't click this button, if
we don't register our email in testers,
and I honestly don't even
remember it, I'll name it,
if we don't register it here,
then nothing will connect, and
we need it to connect.  That's why
we enter our email here.  Be sure to
click save.  That's it, she's saved.
We can click on the cross.  Now we are in test
users and we should see our
email here.  We can't see it right now, but I'll
just try refreshing the page.  I
think she will appear downstairs immediately
after this.  No, it didn't appear.
Listen, look at this.  This is not very
good.  Let's do this,
damn it, I don't remember the email.  Right now,
Google services are the most difficult to
connect.  Well, I didn't click save
last time, so it didn't
save.  It is important to always click save
on all websites and all
services.  That's it, we're great.  So what did
we do again?  You and I clicked on the
three bars at the top.  We
found the Library here.  Here is a list of
connections we can
use.  Here is Google Workspace,
yes, we saw Google Calendar.  If we
click view all, we'll see a
bunch of other services here that we
can also connect.  And let's go ahead and, so as
not to waste time while we're
on this site, click on Gmail and
also click on enable, because we
need email to connect and we need a
calendar.
Connecting a Telegram account is a little different, but you can do the same thing, and it
will communicate with people from your
Telegram account.  This is not a problem,
I will show you in the next lessons.  Let's start with
this.  So, credential.  Let's go to the
connection section to make sure
everything is connected.  What
we have here is actually a web client.
If we click on it, we
will go to Audi, here we will see
us in the testers, here in the Clinks section we will see
our connection.  You and I have already made two
typos: Gmail and, in general,
Google Calendar.  That's it, we're
not really interested in anything else on this site
.  We have done what was necessary.
If we need to connect
another service, for example, Google
Sheets, again, we go to the library
here, as I do now.  And either
we search through the search, or again Google
Workspace, View All.  And here we
can find Google Sheets.  Here they are.  And we
can connect Google
Sheets in the same way.  We do this once.  And,
actually, well, we don’t need to
come back here anymore.  That's it, we've made the
connection.  Now we return to the
NN website, where we actually
deployed this whole thing.  And here we
click on any of these circles.  And here
we click Create New
Credential.  And here we see sign in via
Google.  If you click here, it will
offer you to log in via Google mail,
which is the one we just used to access it.
He will ask you if everything needs to be resolved.
There you click on all the checkboxes and allow
everything that can be allowed.  Here.  And after
everything is accepted, you will have a
green checkmark.  Actually, everything is
connected, you will have everything ready.  I
can't do that for you now because it's a
connection screen and it cuts out during recording.
That's why you won't see it anyway
.  But I already have it connected here,
so I just choose Google
Calendar.  I clicked here once,
then went here, and then again here I selected
Google Calendar.  Here, I crossed over here,
came back, crossed over here, came
back and now I crossed over here.  That's it,
everything connected automatically for me.  That is,
we did it once, we already have this
crinsil, everything is ready.  Here.  Now let's pay
attention to an important point once again.
Since you are using my template,
you will most likely automatically have here and
from list - this is a list, yes, this is
mail.  Most likely, you will have
my email registered here, so you need to
choose yours.  It will be here
automatically for you immediately after connecting
.  You press on it like this.
All.  You don't need to touch anything else here
.  Anything else
won't help you in any way.  It is already automatically
connected here.  You just need to choose
which specific calendar to pull
information from.  And here you choose
your email.  Accordingly, in
all the others you also need to
connect automatically.  Click twice and make sure that
your email appears here.
All.  If mail is connected everywhere here,
great, that means we can
already work with this.  Let's
try working with the calendar now.
Click save.  Here we saved it.
And now we have an assistant that is
connected to our Google calendar.  He
knows how to complete tasks.  Now we
return to our main
project,
namely main.
Here.  And we have a calendar here.
Actually, we
profit from it twice.
And here there is a Workflow list in
which we need to select the
calendar that we created.  Calendar
2. Now I click the buttons, and everything is
connected.
Well, at least everything should have
connected.  We will now test with you whether this is true
, whether
everything really works for us.  And what do
we do for this?  To do this, we click
workflow.  We are launching a test process.
That is, right now the bot
will spin once.  If we want the
bot to work constantly, then we switch
this switch, and that's it, everything is now
in working mode.  But when we make
any changes, it's better to click
save, disable it just in case,
then enable it, and then the changes
will take effect in the constantly running
bot.  When the mode is constantly active,
these green things that
will be running here now, they don’t run.
They are not visible in the Executions section.  We'll need to
check if you have
email connected.  Yes, it's very simple.  We'll
click now
and write to our agent.  What shall we
write to him?  Well, let's ask him
to create a
meeting on
February 18th at 6:00 PM
for 30 minutes.  Let's not talk about who
for now, just create a meeting.  So,
accordingly, we see that the process has started
, yes, thanks to the test mode we
see that something is happening here now
.  We will deploy each process.
We see that a request to
the calendar agent has been made, and it appears to have been
successful.  Yes, now we will
check everything together.  Oops, we have a meeting set up for you and me on
February 18th for 30 minutes.
Let's go to the calendar to
check if this is true.  And we see that
for some reason we have two meetings created, yes,
we had some kind of mistake or
something.  Well, he also
sent us a message that he created two meetings at the same time
.  This happens.  This is all
fixable.  And if something like this
happens, what do we do?  We're
returning to, well, N8N.   Here in
history, all we
can see is the request's path
to the calendar agent.  If we
double-click on it, we see that there was
only an appeal to our
calendar.  Let's go to the
Executions section, look in the history
to see what just happened, and see
why we created two
events at once.  And why did this happen?  We
see that input data has entered our calendar
.  So, create a meeting on
February 18 at 17:00 for 30 minutes.  So,
accordingly, he understood this request.
Then this request went to our brains.   Here
we see that there
were two appeals to him.
Accordingly, we click here and see
that there were two results here too.
That's why there were two of them.  Let me
tell you this, I've never had anything like this before.
This is the first time I've encountered such a
bug.  We'll check now whether this is just a one-
off glitch that happens
once in 1,000 cases, or whether it's some kind of
constant error that could
somehow hinder us.  We
press test again.  We're returning to
Telegram.  Here.  And you know what?  You and I
will immediately write to him: "Delete all
meetings."
since
February 18.  Here.
And now we will check whether it will process
our request and delete the meetings.  Let's just
check the next function.  That is,
if we go here to the calendar, yes, and
refresh the page here, we will see in the
history a new process that was just
being processed.  Here it is, it took just over three
seconds.  Here.  And
accordingly, he deleted two
events.  Here we see.  Now let's
see what the assistant answered us in Telegram
.  All meetings were successfully
deleted.  Let's go back to the calendar.  Yes,
indeed, they disappeared.  Fine.
Now let's try again.  We'll conduct the
same test, basically, as we originally
planned.  Let's make sure that
everything is fine and the bot is functioning
properly.  Let's create a meeting on
February 19th at 6:00 PM for an hour.  Just
meeting.  Yes, we haven't even
named it yet.  We didn't come up with any
name for it.  And,
actually, something happened.  The meeting
was successfully created.  It seems like everything is fine.
Yes, the meeting was also successfully created in the calendar
.  And what
mistakes can we make here?  We may have a
time zone problem.  Then we
click on the gear here, go to the settings and
see what time we have
indicated here, actually, in the calendar and what
time we have
indicated in N8N.  What else can we
do here?  We can connect the agent's e-mail
so that he
can actually send letters.  We see that
everything is great with our calendar.  How is email
connected?  Yes, exactly the same.  We go
to the list of our projects,
create a new workflow,
import from file.
Select email.
And we have just such an agent here
.  He also has a system
prompt.  He knows what tool he
needs to use.  And now you and I are
connecting ail.  How?  Due to the fact that
we have already created, in general,
an account on Google Cloud and we have already made an
IP connection, everything
will happen here automatically.  That is, you and I have
selected the Create New Creedential connection here
.  Google was also connected,
I already have it, so there is no need to
do this.  So I walked through the fields and
looked at what was here.  Well
, in general, everything is fine.  Now
quickly like this.  Oops, clicked here.
Now to the empty window.  Click here,
go back.  Clicked here.
Well, that's how simple it all connects.   The
beauty of AI assistants is that when
you train them, you train them once and
then they work reliably.  But you
teach people and then they leave unpleasantly.
So, a title is required.  The name
is required.  Here we have added a new file.
We should write that this is email 2 in
my case.  That's it, it's preserved
perfectly.  We just connected all the mails with
you, uh.  Well, that's all we've
pressed.  Let's check if
the mail is working.  That's why we
come back.  So, what do we have here?  This is
our calendar agent.  I close it so that it doesn't get in the way of my
tabs.  Here I
click test workflow again.  A, to
see the window.  And, uh, me Yeah, test.
Wait, we're stopping the test.  First, we
need to go here to the email agent and here
in the list select our email
2, which we just made so that
it will contact it when it is
necessary to work with the mail.
Well, actually, mail is very easy
to connect here.  Now workflow.
And let's write a command to him.
Here, write to me by email.   This one
.
What should you write?  Come on,
write it.
Hello.  That's
when I can meet you.  Let's say that this is
our request.
We are not discussing the subject of the letter yet.
We simply wrote him an email, sent
a request, and we see that he contacted an
email agent.  Just in case, we immediately
go to Execution in the email agent, go
to the history and see what's
going on here.  We see that everything happened
successfully.  If there was an error, then by
double-clicking here we would see what the
specific error was.  That is, what data
came in, what came out.  And here inside, if
you use
n8N.Cloud, cloud.  Well, that is, here is this
cloud thing, which is
given away for free for 14 days, then you
also have artificial intelligence here,
which can
tell you about some errors in English.  But in
such cases, I usually just go to the GPT chat
and explain to him, look, I have a
project in N8N, I’m doing this, this, this
, I got this error,
explain what the problem is.  Here.
And despite the fact that I am mostly in the States
, I still do
n’t know English perfectly.  And many
things are completely [ __ ] incomprehensible to me.  And
so I just Ctrl C, Ctrl V in the
GPT chat and ask, he translates, explains,
and I'm like: "Ah, so it's all
written right here."  That is, the beauty of this thing is
that if any errors
arise, they are usually already very clear
.  They just need to be translated.  And if you
don’t understand, then a little ingenuity of the GPT and everything
flies, and everything is ready.  So, we see that
everything was processed successfully here.  Well,
let's get back to Telegram.  He says
that the letter was sent successfully, and the email I
indicated here is, well, my
test email, yes, to make sure
that everything works.  So we go to our inbox
and see that, yes,
indeed, a letter has arrived:
"Hello, when can I meet with you?
Respectfully, why does he write
with respect, Tom? How does he know that's
my name?"  The thing is that
if we go to the agent's email in the
system prompt here,
then, well, and expand it to full screen,
then we will carefully see that here
I have the name Tom.  Here.  And if you
look closely at what is
written here, and look closely at
each system prompt, at each
instruction, and translate it if you
don’t know English, then you will see where
exactly my name is, where it is
mentioned, where exactly it takes into account
and what parameters are there.  I recommend
figuring out this internal system
prop, uh, because it is the
main thing that makes
everything work correctly and is properly
organized.  That is, we see that
the letter has been sent, we have successfully
connected everything with just a few
clicks.  Well, good.  OK.  What
else don't we have here?  The calculator
is connected very simply.  It's already
connected.  Why is there a calculator here?  The
thing is that the brains we
rent from Open AI,
this GPT model, they don’t always
calculate well.  Here.  And they sometimes have
problems with mathematics.  That's why we
use a calculator.  Now, for
everything to work, we just need to
connect the last two tools.
This is Teveli, a familiar thing for
searching the Internet.  And here we know
that we need to insert the IP key.  To do
this, we return to our
assistant, which we created in the
last lesson.  And here at the bottom
we copy, actually, our key
carefully, without quotation marks, without spaces,
so that everything is there.  Press Ctrl C,
return to our agent right here
.  And instead of the word K we insert our IP
key.  Okay, we've connected Tevili, but with the
agent contact, things are more
interesting here.  Look, we're
connected here,
which means we have another assistant for working with
contacts.  So what do we do?  We
return to the menu, click
create workflow, three dots,
import from file and import
our agent contact, which is connected
to the Air Table database.  We see that
this agent also turns on when
our assistant calls it.  He has
brains.  This is the 4o mini model.
Everything is already connected here.  And he has
the ability to work with a database.  That
is, extract contacts from this
table, for example, add them, change
and adjust them.  Why are we
using any other service here and not
Google Sheets?  Yes, because Google
Sheets are easy to connect.  I already
explained how to access Google Cloud,
how to select and that's it.  And you use
the database.  But there are also other
platforms and services, such as Air Table.
What is this?  This is a thing like this
, which also connects via an IP key
.  We click Create New
Credential.  We see that you can
insert a token here.  Where do we get this token?   Let
's go to airtable.com.
And here we have it, now I’ll go back
.  Here we have, in general, a
table.  I created it.  Let's
create a new one so that it's clear to you,
because there is a nuance there.  Create a new
empty table.  Here.  And here we see
that we already have some unnecessary
fields.  We delete them.  We don't need them to
connect contacts.  We
only need two fields now.
This is the name and this is the
email.
So,
let's delete everything unnecessary
and connect mail.  She's on the
list here.  We need to
click here like this: email and give it a name: email.
Be sure to use lowercase letters.  I'll
explain why small.  Because
we have variables in our template.  And
if you write something differently somewhere
, for example, with a capital letter
instead of a lowercase one, it may
stop working for you.  That's why here we
also write name with a lowercase letter.
Here.  And in fact, we have just created
our first database together.  We
have a table.  What do we need to
connect it to our template?  We
click here on our account and look for
Builder Hub.  Click Builder Hub and
go to the section where you can get an IP
key.  To do this, we click here to create a new
token and come up with a name for it.  We have
this main thing there, yes, it’s called a project,
so we’ll also make an addope.  And here
we add everything.  So, that is, carefully,
scrolling through everything, we add so that
he has all the permissions.  Then
we’ll figure out what it is, where it goes, and why.
You don't need this now.  You add everything here,
select the table you created.  Here
we have created, I have two identical ones here,
but, in my opinion, this last one is
new.  All.  And we gave access to this
table.  Click create token.
Let me do this with you now
so that we have a normal
connection, so that everything works properly for both
you and me.  Then I will be
calm, I will know that it was not in vain that I
recorded this lesson and told everyone about everything.
Here we have added everything, and also
made a table.  Click Create token.  We received the
code, copy it.  We return to N8N.
Insert the key here.  Click
"Save".  Check mark.  That's it, we've
connected everything.  We just got everything
working.  But here we need to select a
database.
Here we select the base, here is the table,
which, yes, we created.  We select
that everything is connected.  Here
untitle buy stable one.  Let's go
back and see if this is exactly what
we're talking about now,
connecting.
Attention is important here.
Here.  Yes, it is a purple logo,
basically.  Table one.  Indeed, this is the
name.  Name, email - this is what
you and I created.  Everything is cool.  Okay,
fine.  Then let's go back.  Here
we have everything connected.  We are convinced that
we have already made a choice here.  And here again
we press twice, we have a ready-made
account connected, everything is fine.  So
, we also select our database.  We have it
in the form of a table.  Everything is connected.
Here we have name email address.  Everything is fine.   We do
n't touch anything here.  And then all
we have to do is save the stop
name.  Don't forget
to sign the name of everything.
Here is contact
contact 2. That's it, we have it saved.
Now we need to test.  So,
for this we return to our
main agent.  Here.  Click on contacts.
Here we select contact 2. This is exactly the
assistant that I just created.
At the top, click on the empty space and
click test.  Now we
give our assistant a request.  Let's tell
him: "Add
his email to your contacts."
Tyrdyrdyrdyrdir.com.
So, we gave the command.  We are now watching
what will happen.  We see that a
request has been sent to the agent's contact.  We go to the
agent’s contact, click on history, and see
that it was successful.  The process took 3 seconds
to complete.  He was treated twice.
If we click here, everything seems to be fine.
Petya should have been saved.  We see the
variable name, we see it.  Yes, with a lowercase
letter.  Everything is as we discussed.
Everything here is neatly written, everything is
connected.  It seems like we're doing well here.  In
Telegram it should say that the contact has been added
successfully.  Let's go
to the table and see that yes,
indeed, he added Petya himself.  That's
all.  I can only applaud us,
because we just created a
universal assistant that can
do all of this, to whom we can now
send voice messages, who
can process all of this.  And all
thanks to IP keys, very simple
connections.  That is, you select any
thing, click on the plus sign here, find the
IP key on the site that you need to
connect, paste it here, and
everything works for you, so you don’t have to bother with the
connection and take my templates.  Here are
all the files that we discussed with you today
, they are here.  And this is just the
beginning.  I have
n't shown you the copywriter bot yet.  I didn't show you the
research bot.  I have
n’t shown you so many templates yet.  For
example, I have a template here for
analyzing news.  And
my assistant, the very one
we
set up today, can also call him.  That is, a kind of
universal assistant, with whom you
then integrate all the other
assistants into your team and live your
best life.  Telegram has all
the templates and detailed instructions if you're
unsure about how to pay with Russian
cards or how to set everything up.  Everything is there.
Hugged.  In the next lesson, we'll give
our assistant a voice so we can
call him directly instead of recording voice messages
.  And that’s all he could do,
he could do, but at any time of the day he
could speak to us with his voice in the way we
liked and enjoyed.  That's it, I hugged you and said hello.
o